Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hello.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello, hello?
Kostadis Roussos: Hello, hello, hello, hello.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty, let me just.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I go.
Kostadis Roussos: But, it's a, it's a campaign adventure.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm trying to think what I want to do.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay. What I want to do is, I want… Dude?
Kostadis Roussos: Your room as single dude vibe.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What? My room?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I need to clear… so I have a habit of, you know, keeping the boxes and keep, the things I buy intact. So…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: If I ever move, I thought those boxes will be helpful, and…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I was chatting with ChatGPT, should I get rid of those boxes, and it says yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna… so I even have a box for my shoe stand, so I'm gonna throw it out.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, dude.
Kostadis Roussos: You are very… I've seen this with all of my friends who went through a period when they were single. The back of the room has no art, and it has boxes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I thought it was just me.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no. I mean, I've had a whole bunch of friends who were single, and then started dating someone, and then they lived in, and all of a sudden, their backgrounds, which were as boringly plain as yours.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, that's my bite.
Kostadis Roussos: They're small.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: the couch.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, dude, you, you, you, dude, you, you, you…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That TV used to be my monitor before, and now I… I just moved it there.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, dude, you got some… you got some single dude vibes going.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You should come over sometime.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: If ever you want.
Kostadis Roussos: No, that's true.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we can definitely do that. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, the reality is, you are a single dude, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, you know, at least the room has the vibes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yup.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just saying, the boxes need to go.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: They need to go I have a lot of stuff that needs to go.
Kostadis Roussos: But, I haven't…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: very attached to my stuff. That's the problem.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, yeah, I know the feeling. I periodically go through these phases when I trash lots of stuff.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know, okay, I hate trashing my stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I… I just… I kind of go through this phase where I go, if it's not… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… No, that's not what I wanted.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so I'm just gonna drop this link to the summary so you can read it.
Kostadis Roussos: So you can remember… so you can remember what we were doing.
Kostadis Roussos: Thought I had already done this.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just drop this here.
Kostadis Roussos: Free to read.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna put it in the, Zoom, the Discord, the shared Discord chat.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, this is not it. Monastery… so far.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we'll just use a link called Story SoFar to hold the links.
Kostadis Roussos: I just put it there. I'm gonna go get myself something to drink, and I'll be back in a second, alright?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I went through.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, watch a game.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: I guess, what did the summary say? Did it say you attacked last?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, since you attacked last… Sister Mela, she's up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: One second, is the appRoad20.net?
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. Yep. Yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And refresh it.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: Should be able to get into it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It's blank.
Kostadis Roussos: Hit reload, it behaves badly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah. Reload multiple times.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Something's wrong. Let me try to get a call.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: strange.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Whoops.
Kostadis Roussos: What are we using to load it with?
Kostadis Roussos: Should work.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: isn't.
Kostadis Roussos: Does it at all? Do you have another browser?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: One second.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is this the new adventure? Could I launch again?
Kostadis Roussos: It's the one that says, New Adventure.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Cool, yes, I'm able to speak.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So there are two red brands.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't let me share audio.
Kostadis Roussos: If you want to listen to audio, feel free. If not, don't feel free.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just put that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have the serum.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I have to give you a new link.
Kostadis Roussos: Have a good evening.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: New link? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm putting it in the general chat on Discord.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: North Carolina's Brunswick Island.
Kostadis Roussos: I think that was not…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, that was an old video of what is happening at Meta.
Kostadis Roussos: Ugh.
Kostadis Roussos: Oops.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Peep the…
Kostadis Roussos: People are… people are, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Maybe.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, what does Sister Mela do?
Kostadis Roussos: Does anybody need to be healed?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: tomatoes, particularly.
Kostadis Roussos: Does she need to be healed?
Kostadis Roussos: Notion.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she has 12 hit points, I think she healed herself.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, do you need to be healed?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Mmm… no.
Kostadis Roussos: You do not need to be held.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have 10 points.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. You have 10 points.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she took 4 hit points of damage, so she's fine. She will…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so she's going to THWAC this red brand with her Warhammer. Roll to hit. Roll an RD-20.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, I need to get you some physical dice.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, sir, I'll buy, buy some of those. Quite hard, deep muscles.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Perdium.
Kostadis Roussos: 13?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 13. That is… okay, she gets… what does she get? She gets a,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, what did she get? So, what's her attack?
Kostadis Roussos: What is your…
Kostadis Roussos: Plus 4 to hit. Alright, so she gets a plus 4, that's a 17, she hits, so she does, 6 points of damage.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: To the first trade brand, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's a red brand number 1.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Who is next?
Kostadis Roussos: The person who is next is, wait, where's Rule 20?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the person who is next is this red brand.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, this red brand decides to run.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's true, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: 1, 2, 3… 4, 5, 6. So he's running behind this house.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, it's not his turn, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it is… yeah, no, it's Red Brand, this one…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, sorry, this one was red brand muffin number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, sorry. She attacked the one that was, right next to him.
Kostadis Roussos: Right next to her. She didn't want to take a risk of an attack of opportunity.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Vera.
Kostadis Roussos: It's Vera's turn.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Vera… Rivera goes… Over here, and we'll try a firebolt. Roll an RD20.
Kostadis Roussos: The firebolt flies through the air, but…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This is spectacular.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, this red brand also tries to run 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, what do you want Pip to do?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, boss, attack him? You want Pip… you want Pip to attack him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Pip can only… can't quite get into melee range.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, but maybe he has a weapon he can use.
Kostadis Roussos: He has a javelin.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll a D20.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's start.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that is bad, that is bad. Alright, Xenophon, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Mom.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I can move, like, 5…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 5 feet weeks, right? So, I'll use the WEX.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you want to run this way. You can run up to here, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, you're moving, sister, my wife.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, right, sorry. My bad.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You can… How many? Five, right?
Kostadis Roussos: You can move 30 feet.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are you kid? That is, like, 6 squares.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, which pretty much,
Kostadis Roussos: So just so you know, the way I play the game is if you can move the arrow this way, 30 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: You can move… so you don't have to count squares, you just can drag your character.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I did now, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, yeah, there it is. Okay. Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna use the WEX, software.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Vex, and then, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Forced attack?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: attack, yes. Now, do I do it with an advantage?
Kostadis Roussos: No, not the first attack.
Kostadis Roussos: You only do an advantage if, if you… the Vex hits.
Kostadis Roussos: And then the other guy's an advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: Whoa.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I can see…
Kostadis Roussos: 7 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to use your sneak attack bonus here?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. You kill him!
Kostadis Roussos: He dies!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yank, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: He dies.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Glad he didn't run.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he ran, you killed him. Alright, Sister Mela… Sister Mela… Dashes over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, she dashes to be right next to this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: This guy over here, I'm gonna just put this guy…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, Sister Mela… this bread-and ruffian sees Sister Mela as very committed to killing him, and says, alright, alright, I'll surrender!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so he's alive, and we captured him.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, alright. So, he's currently… captured.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: quite neat.
Kostadis Roussos: No, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Let's go back to the… you now have captured one of these guys.
Kostadis Roussos: Correct.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are we gonna get any loot from these guys?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, loot, right, yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Main Street.
Kostadis Roussos: Man needs to hear you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, do they have… okay, so let me just, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just go here.
Kostadis Roussos: They didn't… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me stop the battle, Sam.
Kostadis Roussos: Joker.
Kostadis Roussos: D&D lender, world map, campaign notes, save generations, combat techer.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Generators…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: You find… what do you find here?
Kostadis Roussos: You find 15 copper pieces.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold on, 15 copper pieces, plus 9 gold pieces, Plus 8 silver pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, 8, 9… Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, let me just, story notes.
Kostadis Roussos: 8.
Kostadis Roussos: Old pieces…
Kostadis Roussos: 9 silver pieces, 16 copper pieces there. I put it in there. Alright, divide that by 4, so that's how much everybody gets.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey dude, the rest of your party, doesn't… don't they get some treasure? Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: At this point in time.
Kostadis Roussos: This guy comes out of the Town Master's Hall.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we're just gonna use this icon for now and fix it later.
Kostadis Roussos: Carbon Wester, pops his head out, right? So let's get rid of these two. These three guys are all dead.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And he walks over there and looks around the corner, quite terrified.
Kostadis Roussos: He says, Oh! Well, who are you?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And before you continue, guys… Hold on, before you… before you continue…
Kostadis Roussos: He says, my name is, my name is Harbren Wester. I am, in fact, the mayor of, the town master of this town.
Kostadis Roussos: And I see that you have managed to capture a red brand ruffian.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'll go, you'll respond.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Harbin. I'm Zenoan, and this is my…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Team. Pip, Sister Mela and Sister Vera.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, we managed to capture a red brand. He was trying to follow
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And then we were ambushed, so we had to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you had to attack! Is that… is that what they're saying these days?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, we gotta keep ourselves safe, Shouldn't we?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he goes, well, yes, yes, and the Red Brands are a terrible, terrible plague on the town!
Kostadis Roussos: It goes, but I do want to say, are you adventurers?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We happen to be walking right in the middle, into the middle of the adventure. So, yes, we are adventurers.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, oh, well, in that case…
Kostadis Roussos: I have just the thing for you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm all yours.
Kostadis Roussos: I have a little quest for you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Go on.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, I am looking for someone to head east on the Tribor Trails, where marauders have attacked several caravans near Wyvern Tour. So, let me just show you where that is.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, it'll be the same place.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'll just… I'll just show you where it is.
Kostadis Roussos: Here goes… It goes over here.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Diets.
Kostadis Roussos: You should, should, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you see where that… you see where it says River and Tortewery here?
Kostadis Roussos: That's it. If you look… do you see… you should be seeing the world map, yeah?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I am seeing the roadmap.
Kostadis Roussos: And if you look all the way to the edge.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: to the end.
Kostadis Roussos: Right here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yeah, yeah, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he says there's a quest for you to do there.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I won't talk. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, and so I will just… Add a note.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll just add a pin here, so that we remember that there is a quest!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is that where he said, a lot of password buys are being attacked?
Kostadis Roussos: Academy.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Have a beautiful day.
Kostadis Roussos: What he said was… well, you ask him what… you can ask him for a follow-up. What exactly is going on, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, what exactly is going on, Mr, carbon?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know, it's not… nothing the… nothing that a good, strong hand like you couldn't have, couldn't do.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, marauders have attacked several caravans near there.
Kostadis Roussos: And as a result, I would like you to go explore what the cause of that is.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Surely we'll do.
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, and Pip, Pip, Pip punches you. Dude, don't forget to ask about the money.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'm gonna be like, why don't you try it yourself this time?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he goes, Oh, I see what's going on, you want money! That's… oh, I forgot to mention there's a reward for that!
Kostadis Roussos: As the town master of Harvin, and a banker, and someone who cares very much about the free, and he goes on and on and on, says, a hundred gold… the town community, under the leadership of Lord Nevermember, has agreed to give me the authority to give you 100 gold pieces, should you be willing to deal with the problem in Wyvern.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… So you have, he says.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Let's gotta talk now, right?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Victor's gonna talk after this.
Kostadis Roussos: He pop… you can… if you want to have Pip talk, just say Pip says, right? Don't… don't wait on…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Cool, okay, then, then Piper's gonna say…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Dude, I'm gonna try what you did last time.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, he tries to negotiate. Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: See, I think the Raven Tower is very far, and the last time…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: who, when we saved a person, whose caravan was attacked, he gave us, like, 100 gold coins, and I'm sure, as a town master, you must be having a lot that you're getting from Nightwinter, and, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay. Alright, he's, he's, Harvard, you know, that is credible. Role of persuasion.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, does, quick piles of persuasion?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, everybody has a persuasion. Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So I just rolled up a solution.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, let me just tell you what you have to roll.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, hold on… Bingo.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Pip's Persuasion is, well, it's a plus one.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So roll a D20 and add 1.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 15 and a 1.16.
Kostadis Roussos: 16. Alright. Harbin Wester rolls.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, D20…
Kostadis Roussos: There's wisdom. Pardman Wester looks at you and says, Well, I see that you have got quite a financial mind in your head. Mr, what's your name again?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oop.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip, as he goes, well, you know, I'm always, I always find charming someone who's willing to negotiate. Mmm, how about… and he says.
Kostadis Roussos: an additional… 10%! Just from me.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 20% of what,
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, he goes, oh, good grief, 10 more gold pieces.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Maybe you could give another 40 gold pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: I… Mr. Pip, you're not the only adventurers that are in this town, but I like your site. Okay, roll a persuasion again.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you roll? Alright, 18, right? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he's… I says, Mr. Pip, I think 40 is outrageous, 120 is my final offer.
Kostadis Roussos: It's just fine. It's just fine.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Like, you know, dude, let's just take it.
Kostadis Roussos: What was that?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Alright, alright, we'll take it.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, excellent! And he says, by the way, young man, I'm very impressed with your, with your, with your negotiating skills. If you ever decide that the adventuring life is not for you, I think I could use a man with your strong sword arm and strong shield for some of my own personal business.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Let me finish this, quest first for you, and then we can talk about business later.
Kostadis Roussos: Here you go.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You know what, I wish I could do this negotiation with… in the office.
Kostadis Roussos: Why is that?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Roll the dice and then, negotiate with Caribbean.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Yes. I would like to do that, too, just for the record.
Kostadis Roussos: I would love to be able to do my negotiation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so, yeah, I think we agreed on 120 gold pieces.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: For the inventory quest?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and I'm just putting a note here.
Kostadis Roussos: So that the quests are visible to you.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: You see the orange question mark? Those are open quests.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, alright, you still have the, you still have the red brand, guy almost as a prisoner, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Harbin says, very well, I'll keep him as a prisoner, I don't know what I'm going to do with him, but yes, I can certainly keep him as a prisoner.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to ask him any questions, or are you done?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Could you give us… well, Mr. Haben, we would like to have a word with, this guy before you put him in the prison.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I guess he could be of, help.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What we are trying to find.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you, you want to,
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make sure, I'm just trying to look for something.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, alright, so the red brand looks at you and says, what do you want?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, we are looking for one of our plants.
Kostadis Roussos: Sildar will… Sildar. No, no, no, no, the other guy, Yano, sorry, the other, yes, one.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Gunther, or something, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Gunther, and you're also looking for, Sildar's old mentor.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sundar's old mentor was, this guy, Larno Albrecht.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you're looking for those two people.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, we're looking for a couple of friends of ours, and I'm pretty sure you know where they are.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, look… I just collect coins. I don't ask questions, alright?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna stomp on his foot and punch him in the th- you know, smile.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna punch him. He goes, okay, man, look, man, I'm, I'm not, I'm not management, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: I know where the hangout is, and I know that the boss is in the manor who runs things, but…
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know… I don't know how to… I don't know anything. By the way, you also know a name, Glass Staff, so you… that… who's… which is the name of the,
Kostadis Roussos: The guy who's run… who… who the other guys were in charge of, so you might want to ask him about that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Good evening.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So… Tell me more about Blast Staff. Where do you have your boss?
Kostadis Roussos: You have your hideout.
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, he flinches when he says that name, right?
Kostadis Roussos: So… and he goes…
Kostadis Roussos: Look, man, I just collect coin, I don't ask questions. I mean, I can walk you to the front door of the entrance, and from there, it's like your business, not mine.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And.
Kostadis Roussos: But…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I think that he could be useful if ever… if we ever wanted to do, you know, break, break into that. Then,
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: then Zen 1 goes, like… I have one more question for you. Why did you start calling us out of the.
Kostadis Roussos: No, he's… and let's be clear, the guy who was following you is dead.
Kostadis Roussos: So this is one of the other guys.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, why were you waiting for us, on the way? Like, what was this ambush about?
Kostadis Roussos: The boss said you had to go.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: How many gold pieces did you get for this job?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I get the gold pieces after I finish the job, so I'm not gonna get many gold pieces now.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Here's the deal, so… If you're going to cooperate us to find your gang.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We are gonna give you, like, 5 gold pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, okay, I can wa- look, man, I can… I know where my gang is, and he says.
Kostadis Roussos: And he says, the gang is over here. Tressendur Manor. That's our hide… oh, he goes, can I, where does he take you?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, the guys hang out at Sleeping Giant. We can go there, and I'm happy to walk you over there if you want.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, question to you. So, is this quest still on, or can I choose him to put in the prison and then head back to do other things?
Kostadis Roussos: You can, so you can do whatever you want.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so…
Kostadis Roussos: So, just to be clear, you can choose… you can make whatever choices you want. There is no… there is no, once you're on a quest, you can't stop out of it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, here's what I want to do, then. Okay, then, I'm gonna put you in prison, then we'll have a good stay in the prison, and then I'll come pick you up when we need you.
Kostadis Roussos: Harbin goes… he goes, How long will that be?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm going to miss a couple of days.
Kostadis Roussos: Maharbin goes, A couple of days?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, is there a problem, Mr. Homer?
Kostadis Roussos: Because, Sister Mela says, boss, What's the plan?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, we… I think…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It's gonna be useful to us, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't want him to die. No, I don't want him to escape.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And, you know, before… before we use him, I wanna…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: take a look at the Sleeping Giant and the Tresander Manor. I want to explore that, and then…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Make a plan to adapt.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I thought you wanted to go at some other random quest. Okay, I'm totally with you, boss.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay. She goes, like, I was, like, going, we're gonna leave this guy here for two days and go, like, do some other quest? I was kind of, like, worried for a minute there.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, no, I don't know if we're gonna be back in two days soon, we have a question, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay, boss, I just want to make sure, because I don't like leaving loose ends.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, you wanna go scope out the sleeping giant, is that what I'm hearing? Correct. Alright, you should probably take a short rest.
Kostadis Roussos: Excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright. So after… as you step out, right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Should I check in the reset maximum HP changes during this trip?
Kostadis Roussos: How many HP do you have?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have 10.
Kostadis Roussos: What's your maximum?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 15.
Kostadis Roussos: So you want to hurt short rest, not long rest.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The short rest, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Once again, let me share. That has a checkbox, I don't know if I should check it in or not. By default, it is unchecked.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so when you're this low level, it really doesn't matter?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, this is the one that I'm talking about.
Kostadis Roussos: So at this low level… let me see…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The one where my cursor is.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, that one's during this rest, yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, it was unchecked before.
Kostadis Roussos: No, don't do that. Okay, don't click that. Now, click there.
Kostadis Roussos: Click on that one.
Kostadis Roussos: No, just click on the first one. Click on the first one. Now click on the 1D… click… now click on the one that… click on that. On the… where it says 1D8 plus 1, click on that.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, it doesn't actually… okay, go… you see where it says roll dice?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Click on that.
Kostadis Roussos: This is, like, the worst user interface they have. Alright, so now you have… you've used up one of your things, and you get an additional 8 hit points, but your maximum is 15, so now you add 5 to your hit points.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So I add 5 to…
Kostadis Roussos: Your hit points. Plus 5.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure. Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I mean, short rest, okay, take short rest.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: No. Oops.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, just put some cups at once.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, chipset point is 16 now.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip is maximum. Alright, okay. So you want to go… so Harbin goes… well, alright. So, okay, so you want to go explore the Stonehill Inn? No, sorry, the Sleeping Giant, right? Is that what I heard? Alright, Xenobon, they turn to you, so what's the plan, buddy?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wait, let me…
Kostadis Roussos: You're having me on the right map, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So here's the plan. Four of us are gonna surround the sleeping giant from four directions.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We… how many restaurants?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Then, we converged behind the house in a secret spot, and then…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: discuss our findings. How does that sound?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so why don't you… okay, so let's see. So the plan is, we're gonna be like this…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yeah, 4 directions of the house, 4 people.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, are we gonna be, like, hiding? Is that the idea? And you're gonna sneak in and check what's going on?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, we are gonna crouch, and sneak, and take a peek if there are any windows inside the house.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, she goes, I think that…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I think a lot of things.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, I think that's a great plan. She does say that, well, I mean, not to say that I'm not all about the chasing around and digging around, but you're the sneaky guy.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I am the sneaky guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so maybe, maybe you should sneak and tell us what's going on. We'll be right next to you to make sure that if anything bad happens, we can jump right in. Does that make sense?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So it's just me who's going to check in… check in the entire house?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, you're gonna, like, get in there, take a look, peek in, and if you see anything, you're gonna call us, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, it's me from all the four directions, is that correct?
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay, what she's trying to say is that you are a rogue and you have very good stealth.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know why I understood that, but…
Kostadis Roussos: And so she's gonna be… they're all gonna be around the house to run in if you need any help. Does that make sense?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see, okay, okay, yes, makes sense, yes. But I'm just gonna go around the house, because I have.
Kostadis Roussos: They're gonna… Yes, you're gonna… you're gonna try to be sneaky.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, works for me. Okay, let's do that, Maya.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It's good. Beautiful.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No investigation and perception.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: A lot of these things overlap with skills.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, deception overlaps with investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, no, no, deception does not.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Or deception on Slate of hand, stealth, Warlock.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Investigation overlaps with stealth, again.
Kostadis Roussos: No, so, okay, so just to give you an idea, stealth is about moving quietly, doing something stealthy.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So here, I think it's easier if you sort of think about it in terms of superheroes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Tell me how investigation is different from stealth.
Kostadis Roussos: Investigation is… do you know who Sherlock Holmes is?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I know, yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: That's investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: But, okay, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Sherlock Holmes is the quintessential 30 investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: But he's also in stealth when investigating, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so stealth is how he moves around.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Investigation is how he investigates, stealth is that he's able to get into a disguise and sneak around.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so the Black Widow, when she's sneaking around, has a high stealth.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Acrobatics is kind of like Spider-Man.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? So, so think of, like, Spider-Man has an acrobatics of 30.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Black Widow has a stealth of 30.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, sherlock Holmes has an investigation of 30.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Or, or, the Iron Man has an investigation of 30.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay, makes sense, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right? Insight… an insight of 30,
Kostadis Roussos: Well, none of the adventures have an inside of 30.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Insight is, like, you know, understanding what the other people, what the…
Kostadis Roussos: understanding.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? It's like, you have an understanding. So someone who has a deep investigation will be able to connect the dots.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: be able to do do something. Somebody who has deep insight will say, something is wrong here, and I know this is the problem, but he may not be able to explain to you the logical conclusion. Does that make sense?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Makes sense, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so, so Insight, Insight30 says, this is wrong.
Kostadis Roussos: And you know it's wrong, but you may not be able to explain all the logical chain of deduction that leads you to the wrong.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So what I usually do is, if you have a passive perception.
Kostadis Roussos: that is above what you need to detect it, I then tell you to roll insider investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Either of them, if you roll successfully, either of them will tell you what the issue is.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: investigation will tell you why it is this is… why it is. Insight will not.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Insight will just tell you Like, you know, plain truth.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, but it won't tell you the whole causal chain.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, okay, okay, fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so just keep that in mind. So, high insight tells you this is a problem, this person is doing something wrong, like, it's like, the way I think about it, Insight says, there's a bug here, and we need to go fix it, and this is how we need to go fix it.
Kostadis Roussos: Investigation is…
Kostadis Roussos: I've concluded, by following the path of the codebase, that these 12 paths cause a memory race that causes that bug.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay, goodbye.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you see the difference?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the difference between insight and investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I know some people who just prefer inside.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, I mean, like, just, like, different… I have… I'm more of an insight person than an investigation person.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Got it, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, I backfill my insights with investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, you can see it by yourself, based on insights.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I, like, I have an insight, and then I fill in with investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, that's what I said, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So, just to keep it in mind, that's what… so just so you understand what they're measuring. So, if you use Insight, either Insight or Investigation, if you're trying to find what's going on right now, will give you the result. But if you want to know the chain of causal causality, investigation is what you need to… an investigation is necessary.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Got it, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So it depends what you're trying to accomplish.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and, alright, so, and the sleeping giant, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me see… I need to go to that.
Kostadis Roussos: You show up at the, the Sleeping Giant, right? It's actually…
Kostadis Roussos: You notice that the sleeping giant is empty except for a bartender.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This is from the outside, right? I'm still gonna go around the house.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a ramshackle… the Sleeping Giant is a ramshackle taproom at the east end of town. Sever…
Kostadis Roussos: There's nobody else there.
Kostadis Roussos: Other than, you can step inside and see who's, who's in the, who's in there.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, okay, cool, then… When I use my stealth?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're gonna use the stealth to try to get into the, the hideout? Into the bar?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah. Wait, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Amy?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, hold on, give me a second, I need to… No.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay. So, blah blah blah…
Kostadis Roussos: Just, I need to just get up the name.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to get the name. Alright,
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: There's a surly orc named… there's a surly orc bartender. She looks at you and goes, Who are you?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's not supposed to happen, right? Because I'm installed.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry, you're in stealth, yes, yes, yes, yes. So you see, sorry, sorry, I'm mad. What did you roll for stealth? I'm sorry, I got confused.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Not yet, I'm gonna roll now.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, well, she might say, yeah, hello, how are you?
Kostadis Roussos: That is not very good, my friend.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see what her… Oh, she sees you! She goes… she goes, Hey, you! Who are you?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you didn't just walk in, you didn't just stealthily, you kind of, like, walked in, and it's kind of like those cartoon scenes where you think you're high… you think the little kids are going like this, you can't see me, you can't see me!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, I'm just passing by and saw this tavern, and thought I… saw the staff room, I thought I could get some ale.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: any of them.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, an ale is,
Kostadis Roussos: A nail is, a nail is gonna be a gold piece.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's expensive, but sure, I'll just have a nail.
Kostadis Roussos: And as you're looking around, you notice, two people sitting at a table.
Kostadis Roussos: One is Halia.
Kostadis Roussos: She is the, owner of… she's one of the owners of one of the establishments, remember the one who never… whose business.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I remember meeting…
Kostadis Roussos: You're hearing about her. She's the one who owns the Fandelin's Minor Exchange?
Kostadis Roussos: And, like, apparent… and apparently, it's the one place the red brands don't seem to… don't seem to,
Kostadis Roussos: to Target.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And she turns to you, and she's kind of like, okay, and then the guy stands up, and he looks at you, and he says, well, that's pretty bold of you to walk into the sleeping giant after you knock off four of my guys.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, well, then you've seen it, haven't you? Then…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, I don't think I have to pretend. Who might you be?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, my name's Rudar.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Man…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: name, though, but so you're the boss for the Forward Giants, Red Brands?
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm not the boss. The boss is… the boss is somewhere else. But I'm gonna offer you a professional courtesy.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, before you… I don't need your courtesies, so… I need to know why did you attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on, hold on. So, so, Halia is kind of, like, sort of backing up and trying to leave the room.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I just want to tell you that that's what she's doing, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I got a stopper, or, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: You can shout, you can shout for your guys to come in, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I was gonna shout.
Kostadis Roussos: Guys?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Catch the escaping person out of…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, so, so,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so let's put the sleeping giant… here's her there. Alright, so, she shows, like, they all rush…
Kostadis Roussos: So they all rush into the house, Salia's like, I'm not going anywhere, I'll just sit here. I'll just sit here.
Kostadis Roussos: She sits… she says, oh,
Kostadis Roussos: I was just… I was just… I was just here conducting business. This is that. I was all talking to my good friend Rudar, having a pleasant drink.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, well, so you are connected… With the red cramps.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, no, I wasn't, I… Rudar, are you a member? He goes, Rundar? That's our notar, Rondar, are you really a member of the Red Browns? TPK, everybody died, damn over, that's it, roll new characters. My wife just arrived, and every time she arrives…
Kostadis Roussos: She shouts that, so just be aware that she will say that. Hello? What?
Kostadis Roussos: I think, I think it's a new guy, he doesn't know. He doesn't know, so… But, wait, doesn't know what? That the moment I come in, everybody dies, and you have to roll new characters? Get your dice out! Yeah?
Kostadis Roussos: Go ahead.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I mean, it would be… it would be nice if the Red Brands died.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, she goes, she goes, Rondor, you are a member of the Red Brands? Good God! I would have never even guessed! Well, I certainly can't be doing any business with you!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, well, well, I don't know you, but I'm pretty sure that you're a very good actress.
Kostadis Roussos: Lieutenant Rondar says, look, buddy,
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, what? How about… how about I give you… what do you need? Let me just tell you something here, man. This town is our town.
Kostadis Roussos: Not your town.
Kostadis Roussos: And I think we could arrange, we could keep things tight, if you did your thing, and you let us do our thing.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's a fair ask of you, and I would definitely…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'd be happy to do that, but… You know what?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Our works, you know, things that we are doing are intersecting, and that definitely is not gonna keep us happy.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. So let me just tell you, you can sort of ask him some questions, right? You could tell him, where's your hideout?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Huh.
Kostadis Roussos: You can ask them, do they know anything about, the people you're looking for.
Kostadis Roussos: Jarno Albrecht, Glassstaff, Gundrin, so you can…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Gundrid, Gundrid.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you can ask about any of these pieces of information. So he's offering information for a truce. You don't have to keep the truce.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, so, what was his name?
Kostadis Roussos: Jarno Ulbrecht is the guy that…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, this guy, this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Rondar. Rondar.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, Randa, I really like what he's saying, like, you know, let's keep our businesses separate, but before that…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do you know… Anything about Giano Albrand?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Children are… You know, Gastav, do you mean sound familiar to you?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, hey man, I said I'm gonna make trade information, I didn't say I was gonna be a supermarket.
Kostadis Roussos: a market house. You're gonna have to… you're gonna have to pick what you want.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, you know about all three of them.
Kostadis Roussos: role in insight, or investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: What's heroes. What the f- Alright, so, roll 4D20, and tell me what… Pardon?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that's, your insight, yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Day 23 times.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, hold on. Okay, Sister Mela says, he's lying.
Kostadis Roussos: He doesn't know everything, he just knows some things, just keep that in mind.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so she says… Oh, let me just make sure you see it, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Find out some… somehow what he knows.
Kostadis Roussos: You can threaten him and tell him, hey, if you don't tell me something useful, you know, we just put 4 of yours down.
Kostadis Roussos: You can try to persuade him, or you can roll an investigation or insight, or have one of your party members roll investigation or insight.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, since it's just the two of them, I'll do an intimidation.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna do an intimidation? Alright. Okay. Roll for your intimidation.
Kostadis Roussos: And, well, that was a very bad intimidation.
Kostadis Roussos: You do not succeed.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm fairly bad at intimidating people.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You in a real life.
Kostadis Roussos: They, Rondor says, he goes like, are you sure you killed those guys?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We've got a feeling.
Kostadis Roussos: You got it like that.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you're gonna give us some…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: useful information, otherwise I'm gonna really have to show if I kill those guys anymore.
Kostadis Roussos: So you basically tell him, yeah, okay, so he looks at you, Pip flexes his sword, he goes, alright, I'm not, like, I'm not here to make… I'm not here to, like, what's the word I'm looking for? I'm not here to…
Kostadis Roussos: So what do you want to know? Do you want to know about the safe house, Yarno, or Glass Staff?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Quick, one second, let me…
Kostadis Roussos: So if your goal is to go hit the ju- the- the- the- the… the… It says…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I've made my mind, okay, okay. I want to know about glass staff.
Kostadis Roussos: Ugh.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Go back.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you think Glassstaff… who do you think Glassstaff is?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: he's asking.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's asking, who do you think Glassstaff is?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know, like, the… Liter of reference?
Kostadis Roussos: He starts… oh, do you think he's the reader of the red brands, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay, hold on. That was not… that was not what I was expecting you to say.
Kostadis Roussos: Now I have to do some research.
Kostadis Roussos: To find out.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'm just gonna be back. Okay, go for it.
Kostadis Roussos: Coco.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know why, but I'm hungry.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So you asked… are you asking about… you asked about glass staff, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: He asked, who do you bring last office?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so what do you… who do you… who do you… you said, Glass staff.
Kostadis Roussos: Glassdaff. Glassstaff's the boss who thinks he's the boss. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's what he says. He says, Glassstaff is the boss who thinks he's the boss.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, who's the boss then?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay, so do you, so do you, do you, like… so his answer's very ambiguous.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? It goes inside.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, well, you could, like, you can roll an insight to see what's going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Pride and sake.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: Bad himself.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a bad insight, but you can have Sister Mela roll an insight for you, so roll for Sister Mela.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sport again.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a 4 again? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, well, nobody has any insight here.
Kostadis Roussos: But he goes, alright, well, Glastaff, Glastaff. He's Glastaff. He's the boss, that's what anybody calls him, alright? Nobody asks a man like that for his mother's name.
Kostadis Roussos: But you're sort of guessing the guy is… I mean, do you want to try to push on him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I wanna push on him.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, a pimp says, boss, do you mind if I do the intimidation this time?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, go ahead, buddy.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll a D20 and add 3.
Kostadis Roussos: And I presume you're gonna help them? So, when you help somebody, they gain advantage.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're helping them?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, he rolled a 13.
Kostadis Roussos: You will listen.
Kostadis Roussos: 3. Alright, guy goes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Glass staff?
Kostadis Roussos: It's Yarno, okay? Some Lord Alliance thing, some agent gone bad. I don't know the whole story, I just… no, don't ever let him hear I told you that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, Glass Staff is Jano.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: This is something new.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: How do I trust you?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yes, it's… Mr, your name is?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: My name is Zenoan.
Kostadis Roussos: I have to say, I'm very impressed with your technique. Can I suggest why you know that he's telling you the truth?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: he's perspiring.
Kostadis Roussos: He's about to piss himself.
Kostadis Roussos: And Mr. Pip has a knife at his throat.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's a very good insight.
Kostadis Roussos: And she says, I do admire your style and technique. If you have any interest, come by my establishment, and I'm sure we could find some business arrangement to come together with.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Like, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I just run out of words, and I'm surprised, and yeah, sure, sure, yeah, yeah, once I'm done with the question.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, now, as you may know, I don't have anything to do with this, so if it's okay with you, would you be okay if I just left this room?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Mmm… no, what's up?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Beautiful-looking lady like you might be of help to us, so… just hold on until we're done here.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, well, of course, of course, of course, I'll just, I'll just continue sitting here.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't mind me. And by the way, I'm shocked.
Kostadis Roussos: I hope to discover that my dear friend Rondar is a member of the Red Brad Muffin Ruffians. Who would have ever thought?
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Meanwhile, he's wearing the red cloak of the red brand ruffians, you'd have to be blind.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I know she's acting clearly, okay?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you know she's lying, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so now you know that, Yarno Albrecht is Glassstaff. You also know that… remember, Yarno is some Lords Alliance thing, some agent gone bad, I don't know the whole story. You also know that he has a boss.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so… The thing you don't know yet is where exactly is he located?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Nope.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We are looking for… and I'm gonna talk to Rhonda again,
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, do you know… we are looking for our friend, Wundren, and he has been taken by the goblins, or the Red… we were told that he was being taken by your Red Bran.
Kostadis Roussos: It goes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Have you heard of me?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I don't know no stinkin' Gundrun.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, where do we find you, Arnold?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh. He goes, at Tressander Manor.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can you take us there?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, yeah, totally.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Don't forget, there's no funny business here.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he goes, but he says, look.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys look like you're serious people.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Absolutely.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. And, I don't want to get killed.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You certainly do not.
Kostadis Roussos: And I was thinking that maybe we could come to some kind of arrangement?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Like, what?
Kostadis Roussos: You give me some gold, and I show you the back door?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: How about I give you some silver pieces, and then you show us the back-to-back?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll in intimidation.
Kostadis Roussos: With Advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: That was well played.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he goes…
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at the four of you, with, Sister Mela notices that Sister Mela still has the blood of one of his guys on her, on her… on her face.
Kostadis Roussos: and says, You know?
Kostadis Roussos: maybe, maybe I, I, I could be convinced for a few silver.
Kostadis Roussos: In the.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't like it. You know, silver is more valuable these days than gold.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I could not agree with you more.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, Tressender Manor. Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, Halia, I think you're gonna come with us.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, I am a merchant.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well… You've got to be an adventurer, too. I see… The Adventurous Messenger.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you say?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: see the adventurousness in you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know what to say.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just, I'm just laughing.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just trying to think, how does this… I want to think how this goes. Okay, so I thought Holly… so, let me just pull up Holly. I don't actually know what she will do at this point in time.
Kostadis Roussos: So, first of all, Halia is a member of the community, so, like, taking her… taking… she's like a… no matter how much you might not like her, and how much other people don't like her, she's, like, a member of the community, so just pulling her off the street.
Kostadis Roussos: And trying to get her, like, you know, threatening her is probably not a good long-term play.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Could I just leave her, then?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just saying, like… .
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, well, then just walk us and… walk with us until the Trickndaw Manor, and then you can go back.
Kostadis Roussos: But…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna tell Halia to walk with us to the Tressendor Manor, and then you can go back.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so you're basically telling her, why don't you, like, follow us, and then you can leave later?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just see, let me just, let me just go ahead and crack my eye.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you're thinking of invest… going into the Red Brands Hideout, yes?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he takes you to a location, as he's… he takes you
Kostadis Roussos: He takes you to a location 100 feet away from the Red Brands hideout.
Kostadis Roussos: And into the forest. Let me just see, so… It's 100 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, like 100 feet this way, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: And, he shows you a tunnel, Not…
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, map layer only shows you a tunnel.
Kostadis Roussos: It shows you a tunnel, alright? So this tunnel…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Let me just draw it, let me just draw it better.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, there's a tunnel. Alright, so there's a tunnel that leads to there, so he's like… Alright guys,
Kostadis Roussos: how about, we call it a day, and I take my silver, and I go, and you guys…
Kostadis Roussos: Do your thing.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sure, fair enough. Before, before, you leave us here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What do we expect inside? How many people of yours are there inside of the accompanying,
Kostadis Roussos: That's a great question. Yeah,
Kostadis Roussos: Pip turns to you and says, boss, we should tie him up so he can't run or call for help.
Kostadis Roussos: Maybe, maybe…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hope… I think we should take him, because along the tunnel.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Because I suspect there could be someone waiting for us.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she goes, goes, boss, I don't know if we want to do that, because he might call out for help.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We're gonna keep him at the 9th one.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you, boss, I don't trust him.
Kostadis Roussos: It's your call.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What do we do with inventories?
Kostadis Roussos: We… well, there's a tree, I got rope.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: He's gonna shout either way, right?
Kostadis Roussos: I got something to put in his mouth.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well then, can we take him along with us in the tunnel, if you can put anything in the tunnel?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you really want me… Gus, do you really… if this is what you want, boss, this is what I'll do.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You wanna… okay, so fine, alright, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We, you know, you know, gosh.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: If you take him with us, we can, use him as a…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Lure, or maybe, you know, as a ransom, to threaten them, if needed?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, alright, boss, I mean, this is… he goes… Because you're the brains.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, yeah, trust me on this, let's do that.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip goes, Vera, Vera says, I believe there is a strong connection between the decision to come to Phandalin, the discovery of Randar, and our discovery of this tunnel, which connects to a… and she starts going off into Hyde…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Fine, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Mela's like, alright. So, he says… what does he say?
Kostadis Roussos: Blah, blah, blah, blah… he goes…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, he goes, if you're gonna go through the back tunnel, you have to be aware that there's a monster there that protects the back tunnel.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Brandor fees?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Randor says yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What kind of monster?
Kostadis Roussos: He described something that looks like this.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? He goes… it has a single… it has eyes that peer up from the darkness.
Kostadis Roussos: And a weird intelligence, and it's malevolent.
Kostadis Roussos: It's very interesting. It's very, sorry, intelligent.
Kostadis Roussos: Vera gets very excited.
Kostadis Roussos: That's what my mentor called an authic. Do you know what an authic is?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: A Gothic is, is someone who devoted their lives to unearthing uncaring secrets, who are reduced to creeping, tormented monsters by a dark curse left behind by Vecna, a powerful lich who in some worlds has transcended his undead existence to be a god of secrets.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Give this look.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: it.
Kostadis Roussos: This is very exciting.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do you know how to kill it, Maya?
Kostadis Roussos: Avera goes, I don't know how to kill it, but it will be very interesting to study it. We could also… it's apparent, they're apparent, they might be… it might be intelligent.
Kostadis Roussos: Rondar is looking at Vera's going, is she a nutjob?
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm, I'm gonna talk to Randar.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You know how to kill the monster?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know how to kill that thing, man. That thing is…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do you know how to tame it? Like, do you keep, what do you feed it?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Give us something that… that we can use to pass the monster in the terminal.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes… Let's see, what would he know? He goes, he goes,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just see… Let me just see…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes,
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know very much about whatever it was, but apparently Yarno made some deal with him, and as long as he was fed, the creature would guard the door.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see.
Kostadis Roussos: So, it…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, this is a part of the cellars, past the… now, but he… now, he goes, I'm just telling you, you don't want to go down there. One of our guys went down there chasing a rat two months back, came up not talking right. Keeps saying things about us, he had no way of knowing.
Kostadis Roussos: We don't ask questions about what's down there. You want my advice? If you see it, move away.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, looks like, Brandar, you know a lot about this Kissandar miner, so you're coming with us.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Here are your two silver pieces.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And you'll get 3 more?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: After we are done.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And, before he's able to paint, What was going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Tie him up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, put something in his mouth, like, time up.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Note.
Kostadis Roussos: Except I put you in the wrong area.
Kostadis Roussos: He's a gap.
Kostadis Roussos: 20 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you walk down, you come down a tunnel with 100 feet. Where do you put the… is Rondar in front or in back?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: in the front.
Kostadis Roussos: He's in the front.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see, I guess you could be,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I see that they're red brands.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I just gave him a name.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm also gonna color him yellow, so that whenever we see other Rondart yellow… red rounds, you know who he is. Alright?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, Rondar, as you're approaching the tunnel, Rondar really doesn't want to go in first. So are you gonna try to push him in there, or are you gonna let him drag behind? Because he's really scared about whatever's gonna… appears behind this.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We're gonna push him with my short sword, you know, forwarding back.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, dudes, whatever's here, it, it's not, it's, it's… it's not safe here, man.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, I don't want to be here, like, could we go somewhere else?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just describe to you what the area looks like.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me… okay, first let me bring you onto the map. Oh, you could… you can see, right? You can sort of see.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah. Some of them are blacked out, but yeah, I can see.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Two bridges.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay, you can see it, right? I mean, you're on the… you can see, you're in the di… let me just, explore.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You're the one who got us through this passage, and now you're saying you don't want to be here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let me just do something else.
Kostadis Roussos: I forgot. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, a cold breeze softly sighs in this natural cavern, carrying the faint scent of decaying flesh.
Kostadis Roussos: A crevast with sloped walls divides the cavern and is flanked by two rough stone columns that support the 20-foot high ceiling.
Kostadis Roussos: Two arched wooden bridges span the castles.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I presume you're looking around to see what's going on?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll your insight.
Kostadis Roussos: Or investigation to see if you could find the creature.
Kostadis Roussos: Investment.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Oh, those characters died, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. What did you roll? Yep, new character. Alright, you managed to… he,
Kostadis Roussos: You manage to see the creature.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can it see… see us?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, cause Rondar is anything but quiet.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna do a quick hanger, we have 2 minutes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we're gonna stop here. He goes… he stops and says… let me just see…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just… let me just do something. I have a cliffhanger for this, this is going to be good, I hope.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I'll bet you didn't know that your friend Pip won a stone shard in a dice game near Neverwinter's docks, then sold it to a peddler heading toward Phandalin. Since then, Pip has dreamed of broken black stone underneath the earth and heard whispers saying his name.
Kostadis Roussos: That's interesting.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. And he wants to find the peddler to buy or steal the shard back, and figure out why it is haunting him.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip turns… Pip looks pale. How'd you know that? He goes, oh, I know many secrets, and I also know that you've come to prey on this cavern, and I'd really hate to have to kill you if you were just to offer me some food.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is this a monster talking?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, it's the monster talking.
Kostadis Roussos: It's talking in your heads.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? So, it's like… Imagine the eye moving, and you're hearing in your head that is revealing Pip's secret.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, right, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. And Pip's, like, kind of freaked out that this guy's… he goes, boss, I don't think we should… I think we should kill this thing. Sister Mela's, like, going…
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at it and goes, it doesn't look too easy to kill. Dara says.
Kostadis Roussos: She pauses and says, It probably has powerful magic.
Kostadis Roussos: And he's… and the creature's like, I just want to eat.
Kostadis Roussos: And looks very hungrily at Rondar.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's certainly why we got him.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so we're gonna stop here, alright?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Did you have fun?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I did, I did. It's very interesting how the creature knew about Fifth, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Well, don't forget, it's talking in your head, so who knows?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Or he could be hallucinating, too.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Or it could emit something that makes us.
Kostadis Roussos: Or it could do many things. So this…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, alright, so I'm going to pause here, we're gonna stop here, and continue, not next week, but the week after, because I'm going to be in India.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, yes, yes. Devyani was telling me that, you were going to India for some storage.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, dude, no, look, so here's what was going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Mono said.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, the recording first.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, sorry, yeah, so let me just tell you what's going on.